Phone: (913)-999-3433 **Website:** https://github.com/jjarrett21

Career Objective

To further my experience and knowledge in the field(s) of Electrical and Software Engineering, by obtaining a position in an environment that will foster growth in my skills and abilities. While allowing me to in turn use those skills to help the company achieve its goals.

Work Experience

Electronic Transaction Consultants, Dallas, Texas

June 2017 – Present

Email: james.jarrett@okstate.edu

Application Developer 1

- Developing mobile applications for internal projects.
- Assisting with the development of neural network processes for computer vision and image recognition.
- Developing enterprise Java, Python, and SQL based applications.

Skyy Life LLC,

January 2017 - Present

Mobile Application Developer Consultant

- Working with companies to provide custom mobile application solutions.
- Currently involved in development of a sports training application as well as a machine learning based game.

Quest Technical Services, Stillwater, Oklahoma

February 2016 - May 2017

Apple Service Manager

- Oversaw the creation of an Apple Authorized Service Center.
- Hired and trained new Apple Service Technicians in accordance with Apple Standards.
- Facilitated a partnership with Oklahoma State Universities IT department to provide service on student Apple computers.

Beardon Services, Stillwater, Oklahoma

May 2016 - October 2016

Mobile App Development Intern

- Developed mobile applications for customers.
- Acquired new software development languages and utilization of development techniques.

Educational Background

Oklahoma State University, BS,

August 2011 - May 2017

Major: Electrical Engineering Technology

Clubs & Organizations

 Meridian Technology Center Information Technology Advisory Board November 2016 - Present • Oklahoma State IEEE-T August 2013 - May 2017

Skills, Certifications, and Awards

- Certified Apple Repair Technician, Certified Apple Consultant
- Computer Languages: C, Python, Java, VHDL, JavaScript, HTML5, Swift, Git, SQL, GoLang, ReactJS
- Texas Instrument Design Challenge Finalist 2014
- Conoco Phillips Hack-a-thon Winner 2014

References Available Upon Request